I'm artist now Jill, I think we're ready.
I'm ready.
We're ready.
And we have the information we're best in the game's lecture.
We're going to be ready.
Thank you guys.
I just wanted to say right away.
Thank you.
Thank you for what you do.
I know every time.
I say something like that.
Because I do appreciate it.
I know it's a responsibility, but I just want you to know that for me, I'm honored.
I know not the only one, but I still feel honored that you guys allow me to do this.
I do it with great joy.
Father God, I just want to thank you Lord for the opportunity to stand here today Lord.
I want to thank you for giving me the ability to stand before this council.
Lord, to pray good things over them, to speak good things into their life.
Father God, I pray Lord that you would just anoint them to do the job that you put them in.
Father, I thank you for our police department.
Lord, I know that in the city of Miami, that there are a lot of things that they have to deal with.
They end and they outlaw and I pray for strength.
I pray for wisdom and I pray for a special anointing over them to be able to handle Lord God.
What they have to handle each and every day.
Father, I pray that you would just put it in my heart and my church is hard to be able to team up with this good but people.
Lord God and help provide things for the community.
Lord, we love you.
We thank you.
We pray blessing over this meeting.
We pray it all.
Jesus name.
Amen.
God bless you.
Thank you.
The generation I pray.
Lord, that would encourage you to stand with this.
One nation.
I pray God.
Wieder this role.
Celebrity and justice.
For public people that are on the personal campuses.
Five.
Cons regulate.
Correct.
We will include five.
Six and seven.
Eight.
Pedels tracking.
Edmonton.
Powerquite.
For Javier Liesonzing.
In him I'm eight thousand.
If you are here, there is a council, and you should have your packet on the VA, and then
describes the services provided.
For this noise, the professional services and current reception, which we refer to.
2020, October 20, 2022.
On behalf of the City of Graham, we focused on the year and year and year in the legal process, including
the review of the recent year in the A&P.
We have to answer the questions in the council.
This will be approved.
It's like a full foot.
A seven foot.
One more.
But when I change word number one, the contract C-21-266 was a circle B-100 ground for installation,
a forced plane from the old installation, the new installation on 690, that's for drawings,
supply, objects, so you want to, 104, so six hundred and five dollars.
How long is this day?
It's been out there lately.
You see it on the tour.
I know we got going in.
And the track, the tape, in the last few years, gives us a city.
They have a different tour.
A bus station on the other side of the road.
They're by the fire station.
And so the pumps down, and then goes on the railroad tracks.
Across the globe.
When they, why in 690, people have to admit that.
And they said, we're sitting there.
And so we thought, we were one of the best scientists who was here.
Right now, we're putting in this, to put the main left station for the Johns end ramp of the picture.
Okay, so we're just north of the J&M's, farms in the cross, well near.
The 911 was that, so we have an underground, you can see how to go from the bus station,
where the 911, the MS is, the underneath the road, and they connect with the 688 sewer,
the force, the bus station on that side.
What you see on the top is what you would see on top down here, and the bottom would be decided to underneath the highway.
So it's going to be going pressure from the right to left or east or west, and then it'll drop in my gravity.
And it was just connected and we part of that same system.
So in the end, what just does is this gives the ability, I think,
that we're going to talk to the combination of names, decided that things that have separate this and that you feel
with whole, whole and haven't, go on the west side of the road, instead of resetting it.
For the extension, so you want to get it.
I don't know.
Because I was a little selfish, because we really couldn't open up that way.
Yes, so we kind of have a hybrid system out there which is awesome, so we decided that this location from right here,
all the way to 69, we could be gravity.
So that's what I want to do, gravity is the way cheaper than the force man.
So the force is just going to come from the top wall.
Yeah, there's a compound that a top wall comes from the force man right here.
So instead of pumping, that gives the old line coming down through here.
It's going to shoot across the road, and we're going to have a, you know, upside where we can keep expanding out there,
because you know, the key was hanging out there.
But then we'll also be able to, when we hook in, we'll also be able to go down anything,
down anything.
Now, if you'd like to join myers online, because I've been here, there's going to come to you that look coming in there.
I mean processing facility in there and some different things, so the ones that you want to cross the road, what's going to be good now?
This isn't right here, all that I can't quite track facilities up there.
So the CMO, the CMO is a CMO station.
It wasn't just one that just was the one that just showed us what it was across the street?
Yes, except on it they're digging it right now, this side right here.
I mean that was part of the 69A YG project.
I mean, this sewer man right here is going to have to be relocated.
So we thought it was going to relocating all the way from there.
All the way to the area where I'll track from there and make that will just shoot across the road.
Where's that real man?
Where's that go now?
There's one right here in the travel down,
69A, across the low-round the Jan.
On Jan's side, and then I'll go all the way,
you know, down, or any of the railroad tracks,
and across the German home.
So if all that's on is now,
how much more will it be able to handle before
is these enough for you?
Well, right now it's going to take everything
from the right side of the left,
so it gets continued to pull that,
and then you can expand.
You can still flow because now you have
everything going over it across,
so that you can expand it,
or go over it,
or connect onto it to the side.
So if they don't file more buildings over there,
you still build a handle?
Yeah.
It just gives you a lot of flexibility,
and again, look like with my version,
without having to relocate it and rebuild it,
you're basically doing it now,
so that you don't have to do it later and move the whole line.
And it's not something, I mean,
you know, you think it can change or I think it went bad.
I mean, I think it's not bad,
it's just one of those things,
looking into the future, saying,
you know,
so we do it now that you know,
take somebody in,
so,
is it?
Chief painters,
there's a lot of staff are we going to have,
we're getting the new ones and the new ones and the new ones.
Okay.
We're looking at the new ones and we don't take the band away.
But of course,
the police,
the police come and ask for that information.
We're just thinking about our budget,
like I've done the same thing,
I'm going to do a project for,
and we've also talked about it every year.
We've been doing that a lot of the group,
and this project came in.
We borrowed money,
and this project was,
and they said we can,
if the council,
if you didn't see an M.S.U.A.
for a group,
then we would have decided to do this
to the project cost and everyone will have that.
Have you talked to the judge
or did they offer to you,
if they didn't know?
We had not talked about that,
but I'm not going to give it to you.
If they don't,
if they don't have any funding,
then I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do it.
I mean, I'm not,
I don't understand here,
but that's good.
What, it looked like,
I'm going to come to that location.
and still in the position where you can probably go in more.
What they don't do, they don't want to send it,
and they want to check it out.
You can put that funding to bring it in there.
So, these would be kind of a block of situation,
but that's the system.
They're building this out.
They're going to do it.
They've done for us last.
You know, if I still ask, you know,
we're out there.
We're out there now.
Because they don't have to relocate that line.
Right?
Is the change word just from the board across the highway?
Yes.
Okay.
And the five hundred.
It's basically all the materials to get from points to one,
that the C3.
So just, but it's just the,
but none of the equipment on either end of it,
just the board and the five to the middle.
Yes.
But if you know,
the other,
the sewer and the water that we did,
down at the intersection,
and there's actually a reason, like, you know,
the state of the University of Esports,
and the one of the ones who learned some thought of the one who learned some thought of it.
So,
It seemed like a lot of people.
I was just terrified of the line on the east side right down.
Is that the power?
The track, the idea that doesn't happen in the package.
No, it's just moving.
No, is that the operation?
Yes.
The left side.
There's an hour they gave it to the,
so the target points goes to the left.
Yes, they're going to go.
What else is there?
What kind of shape is that current one?
I was not here on the side,
I don't know.
I mean, it's the, all the lines.
So, Brad, how long do you guess that you're probably lying to them?
18 to you to probably get something?
Yes.
You know, it's a little bit wrong.
And then all the materials that we can't see,
and you open the cans,
and you realize that we're really going to change the picture.
I just,
That's very much to ask them.
I mean,
we do those.
I don't even think you do.
I'm worried about the water,
like that would be $40,000.
That's what it was.
Yes, this is like $1.7,000.
It's like a lot.
And we can put it out for a bit.
I mean, that's one of those things that we,
that's that, that one on the project.
So.
Can you, can you, can you, can you go change the water?
I mean, is it?
Has it been a bit of a,
What's that on your, can you go change?
This is going to cost 104,000.
Yes, sir.
Is it a 10, 10, or so?
Yes, they're going to total projects, 2.4.
And those are the things we can realistically get a better price,
but I didn't,
I don't think so.
But I mean, I mean, I can share some of their contractors.
So.
Well, I'm just going, I'm just going.
Thank you.
Yeah.
I'm just going.
Thank you.
We'll come back.
I'm just, I'm just, I'm just from bat experience.
You know, I have a board.
If you remember, do you guys have a parade before down the intersection?
You know, we all have one bidder on that.
Well, if it's under 10%.
But we're original.
We don't have to live that out, but if you think you can get a better price, we should.
Now, the price is that he gave what he did this, or similar to the price we had built in,
and then he handed this out. We checked those, so those are similar, as far as he knew it was.
We thought it was competitive with what he had provided before for that.
Let's go.
You're comparing to what he did on a big contract for born and everything.
Just this contract?
Yes.
And this was competitive with that.
Yeah.
And it was a big contract.
I don't realize that trying to give us a lot.
But we're not giving them our material or equipment to run on one of them.
Our main purchase is a lot of the equipment.
The idea?
Yes.
Okay.
We have a lot of art equipment, and you're thinking of, or actually, we're going to retain here in the second year.
Right.
So, that's at 120,000, about 100,000, and a set of $4.
$4.
It's a just labor.
So, it's only $25,000.
Yes.
How long is that for it?
120?
What's that?
40,000?
Probably a household.
About $4.
Could it be?
Yeah.
I'm just thinking about some of those 40s.
You're going down the central level of 20,000, and you know what I'm going to do here.
I think we're getting really nervous about how high we're going to be doing.
There is the big take.
Is it in Rotterie?
Just that.
It's just that the rock soil in the face.
I think it's part of that.
It's just because we're well for the shallow rock in that area.
Well, no matter how far is pressure, right?
Yes.
My gear creep right there.
When they had the, when this photo was taken, we could see the lock in the, the values you can see there.
It's a little bit.
It's shallow.
I think it's kind of expensive.
I think it needs to happen, and I think we do our intelligence and that's on it.
We don't, I mean, it's better if we do our intelligence and we don't get anything with a good thing but at least we can say we try.
I think the problem is that I don't know if they're on the process, but I mean they do it, so that's what we're making up.
Right.
The rest I did.
The rules are anything tied, so there's nothing we're going to do to my car, but I'm going to be wrong too.
So.
When they happened, they happened to change the rules in the interest and the original cost.
I think they're going to want me.
Right.
What happens to you?
Obviously, the one that has to be approved for it.
Doesn't matter.
Yeah.
I can't touch the change, we're pulling it out.
We're going to have to touch this point, because that is the most important.
That's it.
That.
So.
Wrong.
We're going to be laying on that.
Right.
What do you do?
You can approve the change or not to exceed this amount.
Well, I think we'll have to do that.
We'll just do a push-down.
You could approve the motor.
You could approve not to exceed these amount.
There's two, five.
But whoever.
You're going to best.
That's going to be the one.
You wouldn't have to.
But I mean, what's this, I was from about to 1800.
25.
For a hundred.
The year, 180, just.
Just.
Just hear your.
If you wanted to go back.
You couldn't know action.
There's the bill.
It's supposed to be a thing that's what you can do.
I don't think we would.
Yeah.
Back where I made an actual amount of money.
Wait for bills to come out.
Can we get it?
And then you go to the next.
Okay.
Let's begin.
Resolution.
The next year.
We'll be back.
Okay.
Let's begin.
Resolution.
The next year.
Okay.
Let's begin.
Resolution.
The next year.
Okay.
$600,- Daddy.
Ordinary consists.
And so this is for our water tower.
We call it up her dead.
Caven.
Oh, hi.
I want the higher.
Let's just make a.
and the process of stealing and going up.
So with that, Dr. R.D. and there is a state's top problem
in the department, and so with that, we have to work fine.
And so as part of the application package, we have to bring this resolution.
Something to give me this privilege to you, but I agree with you.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I don't know what I mean.
Hello.
We're going to be building this.
I'm going to be building this agenda.
The staff reports.
We're changing the Trustee community in office.
And then the 14 of the people we can do.
From the Jeff Tender, we're going to be in the staff rooms.
We're going to have to take a session.
I think the folks will be getting the agenda.
I'll play positive and the regular meeting for the moms again.